Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Reliable Computing, records
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Stanford University, Center for Reliable Computing, records
1978-1994
SC1233
Stanford University. Center for Reliable Computing.
Stanford University. Computer Systems Laboratory.
3.5 Linear feet
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Edward J. McCluskey, 2012.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
The Center for Reliable Computing (CRC), under the direction of Edward J. McCluskey, is involved in research on fault-tolerant computing, computer architecture, testing, and logic design. Areas of recent and/or ongoing work include very low-voltage testing, concurrent checking of system operation, and synthesis of dependable designs.
The CRC is part of the Computer Systems Laboratory, under the Departments of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, in the School of Engineering at Stanford University.
http://www-crc.stanford.edu
Scope and Contents
Bound volumes of publications produced by the Center for Reliable Computing, published from 1978-1994.
Access Terms
McCluskey, Edward J., 1929-; Computer science--Research; Electrical engineering
Collection Contents
- Publications
  - 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1981 (Box 1)
  - 1982 (Box 1)
  - 1983 (Box 1)
  - 1984 (Box 1)
  - 1985 (Box 2)
  - 1986 (Box 2)
  - 1987 (Box 2)
  - 1988 (Box 2)
  - 1990 (Box 2)
  - 1991 (Box 2)
  - 1992 (Box 2)
  - 1993 (Box 3)
  - 1994 (Box 3)
- Technical Reports
  - 1991 (Box 5)
  - 1993 (Box 5)
  - 1995 (Box 6)
  - 1997 (Box 6)
  - 1999 (Box 6)